Mr. Lewes
An honor to meet you
I am the CEO of Health Biotech
Zoe
Our company produces feed
I heard you developed a
forest frog feed formula
that works incredibly well
I came here today
to discuss a partnership with you
What kind of partnership
200,000
I will buy your formula
The condition is
you can't sell the formula to anyone else
and you're not allowed to produce or sell it yourself
This is also to
protect our interests
After all if you mass-produce it
and sell it at a low price
we won't be able to sell ours
You understand right
Understood
Bought off with just 200,000
What a short-sighted hillbilly
He has no idea
about the true value of this formula
But that's fine
Lucky me
Since you have no objections
let's sign the contract
Wait
When did I agree to sell it to you
You played me
You started joking first
The value of this formula
I know very well
Someone offered 5 million before
and I didn't sell it
Bringing 200,000 here
Are you trying to brush me off like a beggar